{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452520227","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452520226"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452525006","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452525006"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452530622","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452530622"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452535544","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452535544"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452539642","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452539641"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452543417","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452543416"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452547864","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452547864"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452552016","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452552016"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452555890","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452555890"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452561054","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452561054"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452565203","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452565203"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452569875","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452569875"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452575726","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452575726"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452579963","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452579963"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452587393","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452587393"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452593785","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452593784"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452598776","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452598775"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452617040","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452617040"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452621165","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452621165"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452626889","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452626889"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452630357","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452630357"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452634200","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452634200"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452637746","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452637745"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452644340","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452644340"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452650148","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452650143"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c9b1681e-38d3-4feb-afcf-01879d3ebecb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452671028","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452671028"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c4ae10e8-3521-4487-a06e-d8ac0b7ab6bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-7-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452676246","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452676246"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c4ae10e8-3521-4487-a06e-d8ac0b7ab6bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_2-3-0"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452689540","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452689540"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c4ae10e8-3521-4487-a06e-d8ac0b7ab6bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_2-3-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452707519","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452707519"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c4ae10e8-3521-4487-a06e-d8ac0b7ab6bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-8-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452714854","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452714854"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c4ae10e8-3521-4487-a06e-d8ac0b7ab6bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_8-1-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452720135","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452720135"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c4ae10e8-3521-4487-a06e-d8ac0b7ab6bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-5-6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452725456","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452725456"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c4ae10e8-3521-4487-a06e-d8ac0b7ab6bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_5-2-9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452731879","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452731879"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c4ae10e8-3521-4487-a06e-d8ac0b7ab6bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-9-4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452737806","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452737806"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c4ae10e8-3521-4487-a06e-d8ac0b7ab6bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_3-6-5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452743682","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452743682"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c4ae10e8-3521-4487-a06e-d8ac0b7ab6bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_9-8-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452750355","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452750354"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" c4ae10e8-3521-4487-a06e-d8ac0b7ab6bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_6_9-8-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452760289","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452760289"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452769311","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452769311"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452773165","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452773165"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452777146","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452777146"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452780872","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452780872"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452785862","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452785862"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452792105","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452792105"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452799305","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452799305"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452803592","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452803592"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452808402","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452808402"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452812810","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452812810"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452816999","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452816999"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452821347","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452821347"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452826439","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452826439"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452830525","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452830525"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452833928","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452833928"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452837450","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452837450"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452841526","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452841526"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452845773","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452845773"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452849056","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452849056"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452852306","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452852306"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452855534","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452855533"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452862040","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452862040"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452866097","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452866097"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549452871880","data":{"timestamp":" 1549452871878"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453047388","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453047387"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" ac54d875-bec8-4467-8174-42d46b93b49e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549453047488","data":{"timestamp":" 1549453047488"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_142818"," gameId":" 8a82d102-ce35-4b28-ba30-2a5976283f43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_33"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo usishangae unapoliona pua la nguruwe jinsi lilivyo kwa sababu limekuwa hivyo tangu wakati huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}